Daniel Grinshpon

9714 North Pond Circle, Roswell GA 30076 (404) 578 - 6879 GrinshponDaniel@protonmail.com https://github.com/Grinshpon https://gitlab.com/Grinshpon

Objective

Programmer with 3+ years of experience looking to expand my knowledge of computer science and engineering, as well as apply my skills by finding research or career opportunities. Looking for programming position involved with software engineering, programming, data analysis, automation.

Experience

Computer Game Programming:

Space Warp: First real project was a game made for the FBLA competition in 2016. It was the first time I had to deal with a deadline, using a graphics framework and development environment. It was a simple Asteroids clone.

Running Low: Game prototype in 72 hours during the Ludum Dare jam, completely from scratch, using the Love2d framework. In the game you have to move and fire projectiles at an endless wave of enemies.

https://ldjam.com/events/ludum-dare/43/running-low

* Snake_Game: A simple snake clone, made to practice using the SDL library bindings for the Rust language.

https://github.com/Grinshpon/snake_game

* Epee Bout Tool: Scoring and timekeeping tool for fencing matches, or bouts. Used CoronaSDK, and published it on the Google Play Store. I made this mainly for my high school's fencing team, of which I was a part of. https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.HCl.Epee_Bout_Tool

Calculator Program:

Markov: Simplistic algebra tool written in Haskell. Made as a way for me to learn and practice different concepts in programming and in Haskell, such as parsing, maps, state monads. https://gitlab.com/Grinshpon/markov

TUI Library:

* LamBox: Å work-in-progress library for writing terminal user interfaces in Haskell. https://github.com/Grinshpon/lambox

Technical Summary

Languages: Haskell, C#, C, C++, Lua, Java, HTML, LATEX.

Other Software: Cabal, Nix, Unity, Corona SDK, Love2d Operating Systems: Linux (Mint, Debian), Windows

Skills

I possess qualities in rational thought and logical problem solving. I have a well-rounded knowledge of algorithms and an ability to quickly learn computer languages and syntax. I can effectively communicate to a team and perform risk assessment thanks to my experience working as a lifeguard and restaurant supervisor.

Education

North Springs Charter High School: GPA 3.2

Advanced Placement Computer Science Course: 2015-2016, AP Score: 5

Advanced Placement Calculus BC: 2016-2017, AP Score: 4

Georgia State University:

Principles of Computer Science II 1302: Fall 2018

Multivariate Calculus 2215: Fall 2018 Principles of Physics I 2211: Fall 2018

Work Experience

Layer 3 Communications:

Programming Intern: Worked on ONT provisioning tool for client ISP, 2019

Jones Bridge Pizza:

Management: Supervising and cooperating with employees as cook, 2018 Customer Service: Communicating between customers and kitchen, 2016-2018

Lifeguard: Watching over crowds, assessing for safety hazards, 2016

Activities

GSU Hackathon: 2019, Dirst place in our group's category

Computer Science Club, Member: 2014-2018, Vice President: 2017-2018

Fencing club: 2016-2018 **COMAP:** 2016, 2017